nokia cell phones are super mainstream in the united
it's just yet with only five percent of my video
use coming from people stateside the best majority of your
watching from india and indonesia but no matter where
you're from this nokia eight is super interesting
and it's time to review it from the inside
we know the
we'll screws on the outside of the nokia eight he is going to
the first people to ever open up this phone with no two tours
girls or guys its kind of across your fingers and hope for the
best type of situation how did the screen to the point where should
barely too hot to touch and i'll slide metal pray to
between the plastic antenna line and the glass of the phone screen
the wrong avoid pressing the power button during this process
waking up the patient during surgery is not an ideal see
ration one set initial insertion has been completed
he said while avoiding the display of the phone
bring up the phone as needed to keep the glue soft the bottom
phone does have the capacitive buttons and only you tool nyc
those either the glass is pretty sturdy so what's the majority
that he's a has been cut it just with my tool lever
in the glass away from the frame and lifting up definitely